(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
the miracle begins.
さあ！
Let's go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over
ハイになってハイになるまで楽しんでいこう
Let's have fun until we're high and higher
Hyper Jumpin' 運命ごと
Hyper Jumpin', along with destiny
もっともっと近くにいきたいの
I want to be even, even closer
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
It's a live concert where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even, even higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I'm right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' now
さぁ
Come on
Hyper jumpin' now
Hyper jumpin', 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until I'm high and turn to ash
ダンシング Shake it up
Dancing, Shake it up
Hyper jumpin', 空の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to beyond the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live show where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More, more, I want to fly higher
Hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I'm right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper jumpin' now
さぁ
Come on
Hyper jumpin' now
Hyper jumpin', 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until I'm high and turn to ash
ダンシング Shake it up
Dancing, Shake it up
Hyper jumpin', 空の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', to beyond the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live show where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More, more, I want to fly higher
Hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I'm right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper jumpin' now
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう Come on baby
Let's leap across, come on baby
走り出して
Start running
弾けるまで
Until we burst
飛ばして行くわ
I'll keep on speeding ahead
Hyper Jumpin' 踏み込むの
Hyper Jumpin', stepping right in
どこまでも
No matter how far
もっと もっと 近くに来たいの
I want to get closer and closer to you
みるだけじゃない
It's not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from any direction.
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. So close I could touch you.
聖なる夜
On this holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when the four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
the miracle begins.
さぁ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよ
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over it
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until I turn to ash
燃焼しきな！
Burn it all out!
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', to beyond the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, more and more
みるだけじゃない
It's not just about watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
it's a live concert where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I'm right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
聖なる夜
On this holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when the four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
the miracle begins.
さぁ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよ
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over it
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until I turn to ash
燃焼しきな！
Burn it all out!
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', to beyond the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, more and more
みるだけじゃない
It's not just about watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
it's a live concert where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I'm right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle is starting.
さあ
Now!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで 楽しんできな
Get high, until you're high, have a good time!
Hyper Jumpin'
海の向こうまでも
Even to the other side of the sea
もっと 近くに来たいの
I want to get even closer to you
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと 高く跳びたいの
I want to jump even higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. So close you could touch.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
2025.12.21 Sun
Sunday, December 21, 2025
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to participate in the Nepolabo Live
ホロアースからの参加 / 動画配信サービスによる「視聴するライブ」
Participate via Holoearth / "A live to watch" via streaming services
ホロアースライブ開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Event Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
Nepolabo Support Set
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼ特製エモート
Nepolabo Special Emotes
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Nepolabo Live Commemorative T-shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
Nepolabo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
A holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When the four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Now,
Hyper Jumpin' Now
飛び跳ねよう
Let's jump
飛び越えてゆけ
Let's jump and go beyond
ハイになりだして
Start jumping
ハイになるまで
Until it becomes
たのし素敵な
Our own special
Hyper Jumpin' Now
海の向こうへ
Beyond the sea
どこまでも
And even further
もっと
More
ずっと近くにいきたいの
I want to get much closer
みるだけじゃない
It's not just about watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert you can join in
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっともっと
More and more
高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ピンポンパンポーン
Ding-dong-dang-dong
皆様、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日はねぽらぼライブ re:VISIONにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for attending Nepolabo Live re:VISION today.
ライブ開始はこの後、19時からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The concert is scheduled to start at 7:00 PM, so please wait a little longer.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です。
The "sneak peek" portion of this performance can be posted on YouTube.
が、しかし！
However!
他のSNSは音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
For other social media, please only post videos under 30 seconds without audio.
静止画のスクリーンショットや感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします！
Screenshots of still images and your thoughts can be posted throughout, so please tweet a lot!
はい！
Yes!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信、並びに音声ありのライブ本編動画の一部SNSへの投稿となっています。
Regarding prohibited acts, mirror streaming and posting parts of the main concert video with audio to social media are forbidden.
音声なしでも30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
Posting videos longer than 30 seconds to social media is also prohibited, even without audio.
ルールを正しく守ってライブを楽しんでください。
Please follow the rules and enjoy the concert.
さあ、みんな！ 遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
Now, everyone! Are you all ready to come and play?
ねねが描いたタスク着てる人いるかな？
I wonder if anyone is wearing the outfit I drew?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to seeing how all the Yukimin show up to meet us!
ホロアースのライブだから、好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね
Since it's a Holoearth live, it's great that you can watch in whatever outfit you like.
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので、いろんな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです！
It seems we're allowed to take screenshots, so please take lots from all sorts of angles!
そう、普通のライブだと動いて見て回ったりはできないもんね
That's right, you can't usually move around and look from different spots at a normal concert.
みんなの最高の写真、期待してるぞー！
I'm expecting some of your best photos!
というわけで、ライブ開始まで、もうしばらくお待ちください！
So, please wait just a little longer until the live starts!
一緒にライブ、盛り上がっていこうー！ おー！
Let's get hyped for the live together! Yeah!
Hyper Jumpin' Now! ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION 始まるぞー！
Hyper Jumpin' Now! NePoLaBo Live re:VISION is starting!
Hyper Jumpin' Now! ちょっと早めのクリスマス盛り上がっていくぞー！
Hyper Jumpin' Now! Let's get hyped for this slightly early Christmas!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump out
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine
ハートきゅんって Pump It up
Heart kyunn, Pump It up
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin' to the dream beyond
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
More, more, I want stimulation
High! Hyper Jumpin' Now
もっと高く跳びたいの
I want to jump even higher
子供じゃない はしゃぐほうが お得でしょ
I'm not a kid, but it's better to have fun, right?
ねねち！ ねねち！ ねねち！
Nene-chi! Nene-chi! Nene-chi!
景気よく 空を仰いで いこうでしょ
Let's look up at the sky with good spirits, right?
ポルカ！ ポルカ！ ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
宵の顔 用意しときましょ メンション
Let's prepare our evening faces, mention
ラミィ！ ラミィ！ ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
荒波を 乗りこなして 進むミッション
Riding the rough waves, the mission continues
ぼたん！ ぼたん！ ぼたん！
Botan! Botan! Botan!
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating the speed just like this
たどりつく先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
止まらない気持ちをぶつけ合って
Let's clash our unstoppable feelings
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump around
ハイになって ハイになるまで エンジョイしな
Get high, enjoy yourself until you're high
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More, more, I want to get closer
360度 楽しめてるかー！
Are you enjoying the 360-degree view?!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
斜めから 攻めてこいよ ガチなクエスチョン
Come at me from an angle, a serious question
ねねち！ ねねち！ ねねち！
Nene-chi! Nene-chi! Nene-chi!
ネガティブを 切り裂いてくれる センサー
A sensor that slices through negativity
ポルカ！ ポルカ！ ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
流れる コメントと 掛け合いセッション
An interactive session with the flowing comments
ラミィ！ ラミィ！ ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
エイムを 鍛えて狙い撃つ フィクション
Sharpening my aim to shoot through fiction
ぼたん！ ぼたん！ ぼたん！
Botan! Botan! Botan!
期待値は ナナナ 好きなだけ マママ
Expectations are na-na-na, as much as you like ma-ma-ma
邪魔するノイズは ぶち消せ バンバンバン！
Blast away any noise that gets in the way, bang-bang-bang!
準備はいいかい？ 味わい尽くして
Are you ready? Savor it to the fullest
笑い飛ばして 蹴っ飛ばして 準備は万端！
Laugh it off, kick it away, everything's ready!
このままぼくら旅をして
Just like this, we'll go on a journey
たどりつく先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ！
Now!
Hurry up sing up and hurry up dance up 魔法のシンディナー
Hurry up sing up and hurry up dance up, a magical special dinner
Hyper Jumpin' 見ろ 向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', look way over there
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer, and closer
Woah-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh
ドキドキしたい ギリギリがいい
I want my heart to race, right on the edge is fine
Woah-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher, and higher
ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! ハイ! Hyper Jumpin'!
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin'!
Now!
バイバーイ!
Bye-bye!
イエーイ! 良かったー! みんな元気ー?
Yay! That was great! Is everyone doing well?
元気だよー! というわけで、自己紹介いきましょう!
We're doing great! So, let's do self-introductions!
ねねねねから! じゃあみんな、アイテムとかの準備いいですかー?
Starting from Nene-Nene! Everyone, are your items ready?
順番に行きますからね、みんなアイテムの準備してくださいね。
We'll go in order, so please get your items ready.
ねぽらぼで行くからね! いくでー。
We're going in Ne-Po-Ra-Bo order! Here we go!
どれくらい待つ? この準備。
How long should we wait for this preparation?
ちょっと待ったほうがいいか。みんな、アイテムをショートカットに設定しておいてね。
Maybe we should wait a bit. Set your items to shortcuts!
1、2、3、4で行こう、取り出してね! よっしゃ! 3、2、1、はい、どうぞねねさん!
Let's go 1, 2, 3, 4! Get them out! Alright! 3, 2, 1, go Nene-san!
はーい! じゃあみんな行くよ! 飛んでね! ホロライブ5期生ねぽらぼのね、みんなの心の...
Okay! Here we go everyone! Jump! Hololive 5th Gen, the 'Ne' of Ne-Po-Ra-Bo...
せーの! エナジードリンック! 桃鈴ねねです!
Ready, go! Energy Drink! I'm Momosuzu Nene!
よろしくお願いします! じゃあ次! はい、切り替えて!
Nice to meet you! Next! Okay, switch!
切り替えて! 尾丸ポルカだよー! いつものないか? ポルカポルカ!
Switch! I'm Omaru Polka! Not the usual one? Polka Polka!
アロラー! ねぽらぼのぽ、尾丸ポルカでーす。よろしくー!
Alora! The 'Po' of Ne-Po-Ra-Bo, I'm Omaru Polka. Nice to meet you!
こんらみー! ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです! ラミィちゃんしかー?
Kon-Lamy! I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive 5th Gen! Only Lamy-chan?
(勝たん!) 雪民さんだー! はい、そして最後最後!
(Winning!) It's the Yukimin! Okay, and finally, finally!
みんな準備してる? はい、準備してる? 何の準備? 準備してるよ!
Is everyone ready? Are you ready? For what? I'm ready!
らららい! ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんでーす! イエーイ、良量頂きます!
La-la-lai! I'm Shishiro Botan from Hololive 5th Gen! Yay, Youryour Itadakimasu!
頂きますよー! はい、皆さんにバッチリ決まったところで。
Let's eat! Okay, now that we're all perfectly settled.
新しい試み、re:VISIONライブということで。詳しいことは概要欄や公式サイトを確認してください。
This is a new challenge, the re:VISION live. Check the description or official site for details.
今日はでもみんながね、アバターで参加してるし、いろんな角度からのこの振り付け、確認してほしいなと思います。
Since everyone is participating via avatar today, I hope you enjoy the choreography from all angles.
ねねのお洋服着てる人はいると信じてるからね、みんな!
I believe there are people wearing Nene's outfit, okay everyone!
いる! いる! みんなもっとよく見せて! いいよいいよ! こっちが写真撮るんだね。
There are! There are! Show me more! Nice! We're the ones taking photos.
ねえ、みんなとやれることなんかない、おまる?
Hey, isn't there something we can do with everyone, Omaru?
えっ、何かなー? よし、あれやろうあれ! 走りましょう、皆さん!
Hmm, what could it be? Alright, let's do that! Let's run, everyone!
走るよ! ここから。ポルカが先頭で、大きくぐるっと走ってみよう!
We're running! Starting now. With Polka leading, let's run in a big circle!
おっけー、じゃあみんな集合集合! みんな付いてきてねー!
Okay, everyone gather up! Everyone, follow us!
じゃあせーので行くか。せーの! うわー!
Then let's go on three. Ready, set, go! Whoa!
全力! 早い奴がいます! 早い奴がいます! ありりり!
Full power! Some of them are fast! Someone's really fast! Ariri!
早くしてください! ラミィちゃんが付いてこれないよ! 大丈夫?
Please hurry! Lamy-chan can't keep up! You okay?
あ、反対周り! もう一周! 全力! 本気の奴がいます!
Ah, the other way! One more lap! Full power! There's someone going for real!
大丈夫か? こっち半周遅れです! 出遅れてる、逆に。
Is it okay? We're half a lap behind! We're late starting, actually.
ゴール! お疲れ様ー! みんなと走れて楽しいー!
Goal! Good job everyone! It's so fun running with everyone!
一緒に走れることなかなかないからね。あ、ちなみにですね...
We don't get to run together very often. Ah, by the way...
本番の曲の最中ですが、周りの人が見えやすいように配慮してジャンプしてください。
During the actual song, please be mindful of those behind you when jumping.
ジャンプ、ピピ! ピピ! 前の人に配慮して! 配慮して!
Jump, ppi! Ppi! Be mindful of those in front! Be mindful!
はい! 盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが、ここで悲しいお知らせがあります。
Okay! I'm sorry to interrupt while things are heating up, but I have a sad announcement.
なになにー? ということで皆さんすみません。YouTubeと...
What is it? So, everyone, I'm sorry. YouTube and...
ホロアースのボーカルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております。
The free broadcast at Holoearth's Vocal Square ends here.
うわあああああ！
Uwaaaaah!
はい、すみません。
Okay, excuse me.
起きろよ。
Wake up.
引き続き、ホロアースではねぽらぼライブが
Continuing on Holoearth, the NePoLaBo live...
配信されますので、
...will continue to be streamed,
YouTubeで見てる方は動画の概要欄をチェックしてください！
so those on YouTube, please check the description!
はい！
Okay!
で、チケット持ってる方でまだこっちに来てない
And for those with tickets who haven't come to
ボーカルスクエアのみんなは、よかったらこっちに来てください。
Vocal Square yet, please come over if you'd like.
来てください！
Please come over!
えー、じゃあ、というわけで…
Well then, so...
はい！
Yes!
YouTubeのみんな、バイバーイ！
Everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
爽やかだな。
How refreshing.
というわけで、次からはソロ曲ですが…
And so, next up are the solo songs...
はい！
Yes!
まずは誰からかな？
Who's going first?
誰？
Who?
誰かな？ 誰かな？ 誰かな？ 誰かな？
Who could it be? Who could it be?
ねねちゃーん！
Nene-chan!
ねねちゃん！
それではよろしく！
Take it away!
みんな、どんどん盛り上がっていくぞ！
Everyone, let's keep getting hyped!
おーーー！
Oooooh!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The free portion of the show has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!